// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is Machine learning?",
    answer: "The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs",
    options: [
      "The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs",
      "The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of manual programs",
      "The selective acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs",
      "The selective acquisition of knowledge through the use of manual programs",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the factors affect the performance of learner system does not include?",
    answer: "Good data structures",
    options: [
      "Representation scheme used",
      "Training scenario",
      "Type of feedback",
      "Good data structures",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Different learning methods does not include?",
    answer: "Introduction",
    options: [
      "Memorization",
      "Analogy",
      "Deduction",
      "Introduction",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In language understanding, the levels of knowledge that does not include?",
    answer: "Empirical",
    options: [
      "Phonological",
      "Syntactic",
      "Empirical",
      "Logical",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A model of language consists of the categories which does not include?",
    answer: "Structural units",
    options: [
      "Language units",
      "Role structure of units",
      "System constraints",
      "Structural units",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is a top-down parser?",
    answer: "Begins by hypothesizing a sentence (the symbol S) and successively predicting lower level constituents until individual preterminal symbols are written",
    options: [
      "Begins by hypothesizing a sentence (the symbol S) and successively predicting lower level constituents until individual preterminal symbols are written",
      "Begins by hypothesizing a sentence (the symbol S) and successively predicting upper level constituents until individual preterminal symbols are written",
      "Begins by hypothesizing lower level constituents and successively predicting a sentence (the symbol S)",
      "Begins by hypothesizing upper level constituents and successively predicting a sentence (the symbol S)",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Among the following which is not a horn clause?",
    answer: "p → Øq",
    options: [
      "p",
      "Øp V q",
      "p → q",
      "p → Øq",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What kind of learning algorithm for “Facial identities or facial expressions”?",
    answer: "Recognition Patterns",
    options: [
      "Prediction",
      "Recognition Patterns",
      "Generating Patterns",
      "Recognizing Anomalies Answer",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following are ML methods?",
    answer: "based on human supervision",
    options: [
      "based on human supervision",
      "supervised Learning",
      "semi-reinforcement Learning",
      "All of the above",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In Model based learning methods, an iterative process takes place on the ML models that are built based on various model parameters, called ?",
    answer: "hyperparameters",
    options: [
      "mini-batches",
      "optimizedparameters",
      "hyperparameters",
      "superparameters",
    ]
  },

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },

];